westcoastshaving.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Notice

| 

|  |  |  Home > Privacy Notice  
---  
Privacy Notice  
   
|  | **Privacy Notice** |     
---|---  
West Coast Shaving (WCS) takes your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using this web site. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as "data" below) that may be collected by this site. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by WCS, nor does it apply to persons that are not employees or agents of WCS, or that are not under the control of WCS. Please take time to read this site's Terms of use. 

Our secure servers protect your information using advanced encryption techniques and firewall technology. 

Registration for an account on this site requires only a valid e-mail address, address and phone number. You are not required to provide any other information if you do not want to. Please be aware that information you provide will not be displayed on this web site intentionally, however may be displayed unintentionally (subsequent to a successful act of intrusion by a third party). However, the WCS has taken all precautions to prevent intrusion (software patches, private SSL certificate, etc...) As on many web sites, the WCS may also automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address, and cookie information.

We use "cookies" to keep track of your current shopping session to personalize your experience and so that you may retrieve your shopping cart at any time.

You are provided with the ability to edit the information stored for your user account information during registration, by visiting your user account control panel. Please see the site's Terms of use for more information.

All documents with personal information not shipped directly to you with your order are shredded.  

Changes may be made to this policy from time to time. You will be notified of substantial changes to this policy either by through the posting of a prominent announcement on the site, and/or by a mail message sent to the e-mail address you have provided, which is stored within your user settings.  
  
^ Top  
  
* * *  

| New Products  
---  
  
Taylor of Old Bond Street Shaving Cream Bowl, Natural  
  
Edwin Jagger DE Safety Razor, 'Extra Grip' Handle, Diamond Chrome  
  
Pacific Shaving Caffeinated Aftershave Moisturizer
